Pin-Yen Huang

Undergraduate Student

I am a 3rd year Undergraduate Student in the Department of Computer Science at National Chengchi University, Taipei City, Taiwan. I'm deeply interest in the study of Deep Learning, it would be really great if I could assist in any ongoing project related to it. I describe myself as a genuinely motivated and enthusiastic person to carry out research work so as to enhance my technical skills and to contribute positively to the research going on in this field.



pm.binary@gmail.com 🔀

Taipei, Taiwan 👂

09 October, 1997 ### pm25.github.io

linkedin.com/in/PM-Huang in

live:jason199786109

github.com/PM25

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant

National Quemoy University

09/2018 - Present

Kinmen County, Taiwan

Research Assistant

Taipei Municipal University of Education

09/2017 – Present

Taipei City, Taiwan

Achievements/Tasks

 Evaluation of Secrecy Rate in Cooperative Communication System

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree, Computer ScienceNational Chengchi University

09/2018 - Present

Taipei City, Taiwan

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science and Information Engineering National Chi Nan University

09/2019 - 07/2018

Nantou County, Taiwan

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Deep Reinforcement-Learning in Portfolio Management (03/2019 – Present)

Deep Learning for Classical Chinese Named Entity Recognition (02/2019 – Present)

Independent Study

Visualization of Classical Problem of Synchronization in Operating System (09/2018 – 11/2018)

CERTIFICATES

Collegiate Programming Examination (03/2018)
Top 1%

Toeic (12/2017) 850/990

LANGUAGES

INTERESTS

Deep Learning Computer Vision

Algorithm

Research